Guide to the Erica Jong papers,
Rare Book and Manuscript Library Columbia University Libraries
- Series II: Writings, 1937-2011
  - Subseries II.3: Non-Fiction, 1937-1999
    - Essays, 1967-1999
      - "Human Rights and the Artist", 1998 (Box 52, Folder 14)
      - "Imagining Utopia (or If Women Ruled the World)"-- New Woman, 1989 (Box 52, Folder 15)
      - "Interviews," 1970s-1980s (Box 52, Folder 16)
      - Interviews, 1998-1999
        - Jane Campion, 1999 (3 Folders) (Box 52, Folder 17 to 19)
        - Corriere della Sera, 1999 (Box 52, Folder 20)
        - Woody Allen, 1998 (Box 52, Folder 21)
      - "Introductions," 1970s-1980s (Box 52, Folder 22)
      - Intro, 100 Best Novels by 20th Century Women, 1999 (Box 52, Folder 23)
      - "Larry Durrell, Pagan Provence, & Miller’s Vast Ghost," Undated (Box 52, Folder 24)
      - Introductions--Margaret Atwood and Sonia Sanchez, Undated (Box 52, Folder 25)
      - "Literary Topics (General)," 1970s-1980s (Box 52, Folder 26)
      - "Lolita Turns Thirty," 1988 (Box 52, Folder 27)
      - "Making Notes", Undated (Box 52, Folder 28)
      - MLA Panel Discussion Transcript, Undated (Box 52, Folder 29)
      - "Myth of Women’s Liberation", Undated (Box 52, Folder 30)
      - "On the Poetry of Patricia Goedicke, 1976 (Box 52, Folder 31)
      - "Places, People & Peopled Places", Undated (Box 52, Folder 32)
      - Published, 1973-1979 (Box 52, Folder 33)
      - Reviews, 1972-1983
        - General, 1974-1983 (Box 52, Folder 34)
        - " Three Sisters: A Review", 1972 (Box 53, Folder 1)
      - "Tagged By My Tag Line," Undated (Box 53, Folder 2)
      - 'Trip to Russia"--Handwritten, 1982 (Box 53, Folder 3)
      - "Unpublished," Undated (Box 53, Folder 4)
      - "Venice"--New York Times, 1986 (Box 53, Folder 5)
      - "View From the Bridge" Columns, 1967 (Box 53, Folder 6)
      - "What Do Women Want?"--Drafts and Galleys, Undated (Box 53, Folder 7)
      - "Women & Age: Celebration or Rage?" 1987, Undated (Box 53, Folder 8)
      - "Women and AIDS", 1985 (Box 53, Folder 9)
      - "Women & Men's Issues," 1974-1987, Undated (Box 53, Folder 10)
      - "A Writer’s Book of Days (& Nights)", 1990 (Box 53, Folder 11)
      - "Writing a First Novel," Undated (Box 53, Folder 12)
      - "Writing for Your Life", Undated (Box 53, Folder 13)
    - Fear of Fifty, 1992-1994
      - Audio Transcript--Abridged, 1994, (2 Folders) (Box 53, Folder 14 to 15)
      - Chapter Heading Pages and Notes, 1994 (Box 53, Folder 16)
      - Drafts, 1992-1994
        - General, 1992-1994 (7 of 36 Folders) (Box 53, Folder 17 to 23)
        - General, 1992-1994 (16 of 36 Folders) (Box 54, Folder 1 to 16)
        - General, 1992-1994 (13 of 36 Folders) (Box 55, Folder 1 to 13)
        - 1-564, 1993-1994 (2 of 3 Folders) (Box 55, Folder 14 to 15)
        - 1-564, 1993-1994 (1 of 3 Folders) (Box 56, Folder 1)
        - Copyedited Manuscript, 1994, (4 Folders) (Box 56, Folder 2 to 5)
        - 'February Draft," 1994, (7 Folders) (Box 56, Folder 6 to 12)
        - "Fifty II/Chaps 13 and 14," 1994 (Box 56, Folder 13)
        - "For Fifty II," 1993 (Box 56, Folder 14)
        - "March Draft," 1994 (3 of 6 Folders) (Box 56, Folder 15 to 17)
        - "March Draft," 1994 (3 of 6 Folders) (Box 57, Folder 1 to 3)
        - "Screwed up Ch 13," Undated (Box 57, Folder 4)
        - "UK Edit," 1994, (3 Folders) (Box 57, Folder 5 to 7)
      - "Editor Notes," 1993-1994 (Box 57, Folder 8)
      - "Erica's Original Cuts,"1994 (Box 57, Folder 9)
      - Proofs, 1994 (8 Folders) (Box 57, Folder 10 to 17)
    - The Gift Book, 1998 (with floppy disk) (Box 58, Folder 1)
    - Larry Flynt, 1988-1999
      - Affidavit of Gail Barr, 1998-1999 (Box 58, Folder 2)
      - Andrea Dworkin vs. Hustler Magazine, 1999 (Box 58, Folder 3)
      - An Unseemly Man--Book, 1996 (dedicated to EJ) (Box 58, Folder 4)
      - Floppy Disks, 1999 (Box 58, Folder 5)
      - It Takes a Pornographer…And Lots of Pussy--Drafts, 1999, (2 Folders) (Box 58, Folder 6 to 7)
      - Notes, 1999 (Box 58, Folder 8)
      - VHS Tapes, 1989, Undated, (2 Folders) (Box 58, Folder 9 to 10)
    - Witches, 1970s-1983
      - Color Copy--Unbound, 1981, (2 Folders) (Box 58, Folder 11 to 12)
      - Copyright Page, 1981 (Box 58, Folder 13)
      - Correspondence--Fan Mail, 1982 (Box 58, Folder 14)
      - Drafts, 1981 (3 of 6 Folders) (Box 58, Folder 15 to 17)
      - Drafts, 1981 (3 of 6 Folders) (Box 59, Folder 1 to 3)
      - French Translation, 1982 (Box 59, Folder 4)
      - Notes, 1970s (4 Folders) (Box 59, Folder 5 to 8)
      - Proofs, 1981 (Box 59, Folder 9)
      - Publicity Material, 1981 (Box 59, Folder 10)
      - Research Files
        - General, 1970s (Box 59, Folder 11 to 13)
        - "A Casebook of Witchcraft," Undated (Box 59, Folder 14)
        - "The Malleus Maleficarum," 1977 (Box 59, Folder 15)
        - "Midwife and the Witch," 1966 (Box 59, Folder 16)
        - Photo Binder, Undated (Box 59, Folder 17)
        - Satanism and Witchcraft, Undated (Box 59, Folder 18)
        - Witches and Their Craft, 1977 (Box 59, Folder 19)
        - "Witchcraft" Research, 1970s (Box 59, Folder 20)
        - Witchcraft in Europe, 1974 (Box 59, Folder 21)
      - Reviews, 1981-1983 (Box 59, Folder 22)
  - Subseries II.4: Scripts and Screenplays, 1976-1995
    Drafts and related correspondence and promotional materials of adaptations of Jong's texts for the screen or the stage comprise this subseries. Some texts are original works designed for visual productions, including a screenplay entitled Love Al Dente written in collaboration with her third husband, science-fiction writer Jonathan Fast.
    - Love, Al Dente, 1976
      - Correspondence, 1976 (Box 60, Folder 1)
      - Drafts, Undated (13 Folders) (Box 60, Folder 2 to 14)
      - Notes, Outlines, and Early Sketches, Undated (2 Folders) (Box 60, Folder 15 to 16)
      - Outline and Inserts, Undated (Box 60, Folder 17)
      - Working Copy, 1976 (4 Folders) (Box 60, Folder 18 to 21)
    - Park Avenue, Undated (Box 60, Folder 22)
    - Plays, Undated (2 Folders) (Box 60, Folder 23 to 24)
    - The Sex Life of…-- Manuscript, Undated (Box 60, Folder 25)
    - Spring and Greene, untitled (2 Folders) (Box 61, Folder 1 to 2)
    - Sublet, or Nobody’s Business, Undated (Box 61, Folder 3)
    - Unescorted--Screenplay--Drafts, 1984 (Box 61, Folder 4)
    - The White Goddess, 1995 (Box 61, Folder 5)
    - The Women’s Group/Love Addicts, 1990-1991
      - Drafts, 1991 (9 Folders) (Box 61, Folder 6 to 14)
      - Notes, circa.1990 (Box 61, Folder 15)
      - "Women Who Sometimes Appear In Group," 1991 (Box 61, Folder 16)
    - Wooster Street (TV Series) Synopsis, 1990 (Box 61, Folder 17)
  - Subseries II.5: Writings By Others, 1982-2002
    Drafts and completed works of poetry, fiction, non-fiction and scholarly criticism sent to, or acquired by, Erica Jong are found in this subseries.
    - Chase, Barbara Jonas, 1982 (Box 61, Folder 18)
    - Edna O’Brien--Novella, Undated (Box 61, Folder 19)
    - "Feminism and the Politics of Literary Reputation: The Example of Erica Jong," by Dr. Charlotte Templin, 1991, (2 Folders) (Box 61, Folder 20 to 21)
    - Hodgman, Helen, 1988 (Box 61, Folder 22)
    - Jonathan Fast Book Cover, Undated (Box 61, Folder 23)
    - Katz, Alan--"Sam" Screenplay, 1985 (Box 61, Folder 24)
    - Later, 1989 (Box 61, Folder 25)
    - "Lo's Diary" by Pia Pera, 1999 (2 Folders) (Box 61, Folder 26 to 27)
    - Maraini, Dacia, 2002 (Box 62, Folder 1)
    - Middleton, Thomas H.--Poetry, Undated (Box 62, Folder 2)
    - Naomi Wolf, 1998 (includes floppy disk) (Box 62, Folder 3)
    - "Remarks to New York Women's Forum," 1982 (Box 62, Folder 4)
    - Scholarly Papers on Jong, 1977-2001
      - General, 1977-1979, (2 Folders) (Box 62, Folder 5 to 6)
      - Holm, Astrid--"The Ambivalence of the Modern Woman's Life-Situation," 1979 (Box 62, Folder 7)
      - "Jewish Humor Conference", 1986 (Box 62, Folder 8)
      - Kloke, Wendy--M.A. Thesis, 2001 (Box 62, Folder 9)
      - "Scholarly Works on Fanny", 1980 (Box 62, Folder 10)
    - Schulman, Grace--Poetry, Undated (Box 62, Folder 11)
- Series III: Personal, 1955-1990
  Early Erica Jong material, including class notebooks, essays, and theses from high school and Barnard College; diaries; and some writings and correspondence are located in this series. Also here are some financial files and other documents of a personal nature.
  - Early Material, 1955-1983
    - General, 1957-1975 (Box 63, Folder 1)
    - Allan Jong Medical School Transcripts, 1961 (Box 63, Folder 2)
    - Barnard Alumnae "Woman of Achievement" Award, 1983 (Box 63, Folder 3)
    - Barnard Student Newspapers, 1962-1963 (Box 63, Folder 4)
    - Bibliography, Undated (Box 63, Folder 5)
    - "Bio / Photos," 1990 (Box 63, Folder 6)
    - Columbia Masters Thesis, 1965 (Box 63, Folder 7)
    - Class Notes, 1959-1963
      - "Aesthetics", 1963 (Box 63, Folder 8)
      - "American Lit: Whitman to Faulkner," 1962, 2040 (Box 63, Folder 9)
      - "Contemporary Lit.", Undated (Box 63, Folder 10)
      - "Classical Drama", Undated (Box 63, Folder 11)
      - Geology 2, 1961 (Box 64, Folder 1)
      - "Government 1," 1961 (Box 64, Folder 2)
      - "Government 2," 1962, (2 Folders) (Box 64, Folder 3 to 4)
      - "Liselotte von der Pfalz", Undated (Box 64, Folder 5)
      - "Zoology 1 Lab Drawings," 1959 (Box 64, Folder 6)
    - Class Notebooks--Small, 1960s (3 Folders) (Box 64, Folder 7 to 9)
    - Class Notebooks, 1955-1960s, (3 Folders) (Box 65, Folder 1 to 3)
    - Course Binders, 1955-1958, (2 Folders) (Box 65, Folder 4 to 5)
    - Correspondence, 1961, (2 Folders) (Box 65, Folder 6 to 7)
    - Daybooks, 1959-1982 (4 of 7 Folders) (Box 66, Folder 1 to 4)
    - Daybooks, 1959-1982 (3 of 7 Folders) (Box 67, Folder 1 to 3)
    - Diaries, 1957-1966
      - "Additions to Journal--1964 & Thereabouts," 1962-1966 (2 of 3 Folders) (Box 67, Folder 4 to 5)
      - "Additions to Journal--1964 & Thereabouts," 1962-1966 (1 of 3 Folders) (Box 68, Folder 1)
      - 1957 (Box 68, Folder 2)
      - 1963-1965 (Box 68, Folder 3)
    - Diplomas and Certificates, 1959-1981 (Box 100, Folder 6)
    - English Course Essays, 1963 (Box 68, Folder 4)
    - "Erica's Thesis Papers and Notes," 1960s (Box 68, Folder 5)
    - German Trip Documents, 1968 (Box 68, Folder 6)
    - Germany, 1959-1969 (2 Folders) (Box 68, Folder 7 to 8)
    - High School and Barnard Honors, 1960-1966 (Box 69, Folder 1)
    - "High School & College Poems (& Stories), 1958-1965 (2 Folders) (Box 69, Folder 2 to 3)
    - International Creative Management, 1974 (Box 69, Folder 4)
    - "Job Hunting," Undated (Box 69, Folder 5)
    - "List of Poems Published in Mags", circ.1971 (Box 69, Folder 6)
    - Literary Guild of America, 1976-1977 (Box 69, Folder 7)
    - "Master’s Thesis 2nd Draft", Undated (Box 69, Folder 8)
    - "Notes for Master’s Thesis--Footnotes", 1964 (Box 69, Folder 9)
    - Notebook, 1994-1995 (Box 69, Folder 10)
    - Notes, Undated (Box 69, Folder 11)
    - PA Records, Undated (Box 70, Folder 1)
    - "Papers: English A-1 and A-2," 1959-1960 (Box 70, Folder 2)
    - "Papers on Chekov and Lukacs", 1963 (Box 70, Folder 3)
    - Poetry Workshop Reading List, 1972-1974 (Box 70, Folder 4)
    - "Pope and Augustanism," Undated (Box 70, Folder 5)
    - Printed Materials, 1967-1973 (Box 70, Folder 6)
    - "Record of Work Sent Out--Poems Mostly," Undated (Box 102)
    - Resume, 1972 (Box 70, Folder 7)
    - School Documents, 1969 (Box 70, Folder 8)
    - Wedding Clippings, undated (Box 70, Folder 9)
    - "Women in the Poems of Alexander Pope: A Critical Study", Undated (Box 70, Folder 10)
  - Financial, 1960s-1990
    - General--with Account Books, 1960s (Box 70, Folder 11)
    - General, 1975-1979 (1 of 2 Folders) (Box 70, Folder 12)
    - General, 1975-1979 (1 of 2 Folders) (Box 71, Folder 1)
    - General, 1989 (Box 71, Folder 2)
    - Book Contracts, Undated (Box 71, Folder 3)
    - Financial Contributions, 1977-1981 (Box 71, Folder 4)
    - "Foreign Publishers", 1988 (Box 71, Folder 5)
    - "Harry Walker Speaking Dates", 1977 (Box 71, Folder 6)
    - Notebook and receipts, 1990, Undated (Box 71, Folder 7)
    - Sales Figures, 1988-1989 (Box 71, Folder 8)
- Series IV: Erica Jong Files--as organized by Jong, 1970-2008
  This series is composed of a trove of files labeled and organized by Jong. Included here are documents and correspondence related to organizations in which Jong was involved; book reviews, clippings, drafts, essays and articles by and about Jong; requests and invitations to speak; material regarding foreign publishers; various fiction and non-fiction pieces and loose notes; and photographs. Jong's original arrangement of the material has been maintained throughout this series.
  - Subseries IV.1: Personal / Business Files, 1974-2008
    These are numbered and arranged personal files, consisting mostly of business correspondence and documents pertaining to all of Jong's published works. There are also some essays and creative documents, such as a screenplay adaptation of Jong's Fanny Hackabout Jones, in the files.
    - Correspondence, 1995-2006 (10 Folders) (Box 62, Folder 12 to 21)
    - Correspondence, 1995-2006 (Box 72, Folder 1 to 14)
    - Correspondence, 1999-2001 (Box 73, Folder 1)
    - Fear of Flying, 1994-2004 (5 Folders) (Box 73, Folder 2 to 6)
    - Sterling Lord, 1987-1989 (2 Folders) (Box 73, Folder 7 to 8)
    - Loveroot, 1993-1999 (Box 73, Folder 9)
    - How to Save Your Own Life, 1976-2005 (4 Folders) (Box 73, Folder 10 to 13)
    - Legal Files, 1989-2005 (3 Files) (Box 73, Folder 14 to 16)
    - Legal Files, 1989-2005 (3 Files) (Box 74, Folder 1 to 2)
    - Correspondence, 1979-2005 (4 of 11 Folders) (Box 74, Folder 3 to 7)
    - Correspondence, 1979-2005 (7 of 11 Folders) (Box 74, Folder 8 to 13)
    - Any Woman’s Blues, 1989-2003 (2 Folders) (Box 74, Folder 14 to 15)
    - Any Woman’s Blues, 1978-2008 (5 Folders) (Box 75, Folder 1 to 5)
    - What Women Want, 1998-2008 (4 Folders) (Box 75, Folder 6 to 9)
    - At the Edge of the Body, 1989-2003 (Box 75, Folder 10)
    - Fruits & Vegetables, 1991-2003 (Box 75, Folder 11)
    - Half-Lives, 1990-2001 (Box 75, Folder 12)
    - Fear of Flying, 1980-2006 (Box 75, Folder 13)
    - Fear of Flying, 1974-2006, (10 folders) (Box 76, Folder 1 to 10)
    - Sappho's Leap, 2002-2005, (3 Folders) (Box 76, Folder 11 to 13)
    - Fanny Hackabout Jones, 1979-2007, (10 Folders) (Box 77, Folder 1 to 10)
    - Witches, 1991-2008, (2 Folders) (Box 77, Folder 11 to 12)
    - Megan's Book of Divorce, Undated (Box 77, Folder 13 to 14)
    - Parachutes & Kisses, 1984-2008, (3 Folders) (Box 78, Folder 1 to 3)
    - Serenissima, 1987-2003, (6 Folders) (Box 78, Folder 4 to 9)
    - Becoming Light, 1991-1997, (2 Folders) (Box 78, Folder 10 to 11)
    - Scherz, 1993-1994 (Box 78, Folder 12)
    - The Devil at Large, 1998-2007 (Box 78, Folder 13)
    - The Devil at Large, 1989-2007 (2 Folders) (Box 79, Folder 1 to 2)
    - Fear of Fifty, 1992-2003 (9 Folders) (Box 79, Folder 3 to 11)
    - Fear of Fifty, 1992-2003 (Box 80, Folder 1)
    - Inventing Memory, 1991-2003, (7 Folders) (Box 80, Folder 2 to 8)
  - Subseries IV.2: Project Files, 1970-1993
    The material in this subseries pertains to a wide array of Jong's professional and personal projects. As Jong kept her correspondence along with her project files, this arrangement has been maintained. Files named for periodicals usually contain drafts of Jong's pieces written for the given publication.
    - General--Periodicals, Undated (Box 80, Folder 9)
    - "About Fear of Flying," 1973 (Box 80, Folder 10)
    - "Actor's Theatre of Louisville," 1988 (Box 80, Folder 11)
    - "Adrienne Rich--rev. for MS. Diving into the Wr.," 1972 (Box 80, Folder 12)
    - "American Association of Publishers," 1980-1985 (Box 80, Folder 13)
    - "The American Book Awards," 1979-1981 (Box 80, Folder 14)
    - "American Federation of Television and Radio Artists," 1987 (Box 80, Folder 15)
    - "American Poetry Review," 1972-1974 (Box 80, Folder 16)
    - "Anne Sexton (about her)," 1976-1986 (Box 80, Folder 17)
    - "Anne Sexton rev. of Death Notebooks-MS. mag," 1974-1980 (Box 80, Folder 18)
    - "Anthologies," 1987-1988 (Box 80, Folder 19)
    - "Antonia Fraser," Undated (Box 80, Folder 20)
    - "Ararat Review," 1983 (Box 80, Folder 21)
    - "Are You Faithful Darling?" 1987-1989 (Box 80, Folder 22)
    - "The Artist and the Law," 1976 (Box 81, Folder 1)
    - "Artist as Housewife," 1972 (Box 81, Folder 2)
    - "At the Edge of the Body," 1978-1986 (Box 81, Folder 3)
    - "Author's Guild," 1988-1993, (7 Folders) (Box 81, Folder 4 to 10)
    - "Back in the Fifties," 1980s (Box 81, Folder 11)
    - "Best Reviews," 1973-1980 (Box 81, Folder 12)
    - "Betty Friedan," 1981 (Box 81, Folder 13)
    - "Blood and Guts," 1976-1979 (Box 81, Folder 14)
    - "Book Digest," 1975-1981 (Box 81, Folder 15)
    - "Books Donated," 1978-1985 (Box 81, Folder 16)
    - "The Book, the Book (Library of Congress Study)," 1978-1983 (Box 81, Folder 17)
    - "Books Donated", 1978-1985 (Box 81, Folder 18)
    - "Bookviews," 1978 (Box 81, Folder 19)
    - "Bridgeport Post," 1979-1980 (Box 81, Folder 20)
    - "Casanova (Intro)," 1983-1984 (Box 81, Folder 21)
    - "Caveat Lector," 1973 (Box 81, Folder 22)
    - "Chicago Tribune," 1984 (Box 81, Folder 23)
    - "Colette," 1975 (Box 81, Folder 24)
    - "Colette: Intoxicating Freedom," 1975 (Box 81, Folder 25)
    - "Colette: review of Crosland biog for MS. Mag.", 1973 (Box 81, Folder 26)
    - "Columbia Forum," 1972-1974 (Box 81, Folder 27)
    - "Confessions of a Librophiliac," 1979 (Box 81, Folder 28)
    - "Cooking with the One You Love," 1977 (Box 81, Folder 29)
    - "Cosmopolitan," 1977-1985 (Box 82, Folder 1)
    - "COUP (short story)," Undated (Box 82, Folder 2)
    - "Creative Artists Public Service Program," 1971-1976 (Box 82, Folder 3)
    - "The Crossing Press," 1973 (Box 82, Folder 4)
    - "Current Publicity," Undated (Box 82, Folder 5)
    - "Daughters: Essay," Undated (Box 82, Folder 6)
    - "Donna Juan's Lament," 1987 (Box 82, Folder 7)
    - "Doris Lessing--review," 1972, Undated (Box 82, Folder 8)
    - "Duplicates (essays)," 1974-1981 (Box 82, Folder 9)
    - "Elaine Showalter (A Lit. of Their Own)," 1977 (Box 82, Folder 10)
    - "Enduring Fascination of the Younger Man," 1985 (Box 82, Folder 11)
    - "Equal Rights Amendment", 1978 (Box 82, Folder 12)
    - "Erica Jong Pending," 1980-1986 (2 Folders) (Box 82, Folder 13 to 14)
    - "ESSAYS (Extras)," 1974-1977 (Box 82, Folder 15)
    - "ESSAYS (pub. & unpub.)," 1975-1986, (2 Folders) (Box 82, Folder 16 to 17)
    - "Fanny Hill Intro," 1978-1979 (Box 82, Folder 18)
    - "Finding Sylvia Plath's Voice," 1973 (Box 82, Folder 19)
    - "Finished Work," Undated (Box 82, Folder 20)
    - "Fischer Verlag (German Publisher)" 1976-1980, (2 Folders) (Box 82, Folder 21 to 22)
    - "Forbidden City: Venice," 1980 (Box 82, Folder 23)
    - "For My Daughter on her Second Birthday," 1980 (Box 82, Folder 24)
    - "Freedom Not to Lie," 1978-1981 (Box 82, Folder 25)
    - "Glamour," 1983-1988 (Box 82, Folder 26)
    - "Gleasner, Diana," 1978-1981 (Box 82, Folder 27)
    - "Goddess Rising," 1981-1986 (Box 82, Folder 28)
    - "Harper's Magazine," 1984-1986 (Box 82, Folder 29)
    - "Henry Miller Op-Ed piece," 1974 (Box 82, Folder 30)
    - "Hite Report, 1976-1979 (Box 83, Folder 1)
    - "Hofstra Writers Conference," 1974 (Box 83, Folder 2)
    - "If Women Ruled the World," 1989 (Box 83, Folder 3)
    - "Increasing Readership," 1979 (Box 83, Folder 4)
    - "Interviews," 1977-1988, (2 Folders) (Box 83, Folder 5 to 6)
    - "James Chace," 1983-1984 (Box 83, Folder 7)
    - "Jane Fonda--Ladies Home Journal," 1983-1988, (2 Folders) (Box 83, Folder 8 to 9)
    - "Joyce Carol Oates," 1984 (Box 83, Folder 10)
    - "Konglomerati Press," 1978-1979 (Box 83, Folder 11)
    - "LA Times", 1976-1986 (Box 83, Folder 12)
    - "Los Angeles Magazine", 1979 (Box 83, Folder 13)
    - "Lecture Trips," 1988-1989 (Box 83, Folder 14)
    - "Letter from the Author to the Reader, Re HTSYOL," 1977 (Box 83, Folder 15)
    - "Letters About Women Writers," 1977, 1979 (Box 83, Folder 16)
    - "Library of Congress Reading Study," 1984 (Box 83, Folder 17)
    - "Literary Guild," 1976 (Box 83, Folder 18)
    - "Lolita Intro," 1987-1988, (2 Folders) (Box 83, Folder 19 to 20)
    - "London Trip," 1994 (Box 83, Folder 21)
    - "Lonnie Barbach--Review," Undated (Box 83, Folder 22)
    - "Love Al Dente," 1976-1977, (2 Folders) (Box 83, Folder 23 to 24)
    - Magazine Littéraire: Vladimir Nabokov," 1986 (Box 83, Folder 25)
    - "Magazine Publisher's Association," 1975 (Box 83, Folder 26)
    - "Magic Transparent Tape (essay)," 1974 (Box 83, Folder 27)
    - "Making Ends Meet (review)," 1976 (Box 83, Folder 28)
    - "Marge Piercy--Judith Leet," 1976 (Box 83, Folder 29)
    - Massachusetts Review, 1973 (Box 83, Folder 30)
    - "Moll Flanders Intro," Undated (Box 84, Folder 1)
    - "the moon in its flight --short story," Undated (Box 84, Folder 2)
    - "More International Cultural Seminar--Tokyo" 1977-1978 (photos) (Box 84, Folder 3)
    - "MS (magazine)," 1972-1982 (Box 84, Folder 4)
    - "Myth of Women's Liberation in Amer.," Undated (Box 84, Folder 5)
    - The Nation, 1970-1972 (Box 84, Folder 6)
    - The New Republic, 1978-1980 (Box 84, Folder 7)
    - New Woman Mag., 1985-1987 (Box 84, Folder 8)
    - Newsday, 1984-1985 (Box 84, Folder 9)
    - Newsweek, 1977-1988 (Box 84, Folder 10)
    - New Yorker, 1975-1983 (Box 84, Folder 11)
    - New York Magazine, 1974 (Box 84, Folder 12)
    - New York Quarterly, 1973-1980 (Box 84, Folder 13)
    - New York Times, 1972-1994, (2 Folders) (Box 84, Folder 14 to 15)
    - New York Times Book Review, 1976-1986, (2 Folders) (Box 84, Folder 16 to 17)
    - "The Oldest Revolution," Undated (Box 84, Folder 18)
    - "On Being a Cover Girl," Undated (Box 84, Folder 19)
    - "Papa: A Memoir," 1981-1982 (Box 84, Folder 20)
    - Parade, 1980-1981 (Box 84, Folder 21)
    - The Paris Review, 1975-1981 (Box 84, Folder 22)
    - "Parker Ladd," 1979-1980 (Box 85, Folder 1)
    - Partisan Review, 1973-1974 (Box 85, Folder 2)
    - Penthouse, 1975 (Box 85, Folder 3)
    - "Plath," 1971-1986, (2 Folders) (Box 85, Folder 4 to 5)
    - Playboy Magazine, 1975-1988, (5 Folders) (Box 85, Folder 6 to 10)
    - Ploughshares, 1987 (Box 85, Folder 11)
    - "Poems--Subsidiary Rights (Holt)," 1973-1974 (Box 85, Folder 12)
    - Poetry (Chicago)," 1965-1978 (Box 85, Folder 13)
    - "Poetry Society of America," 1971-1972 (Box 85, Folder 14)
    - Poets & Writers, 1977-1987, (4 Folders) (Box 85, Folder 15 to 18)
    - "The Prince & the Virgin," 1981 (Box 85, Folder 19)
    - "Publicity," 1973-1976 (Box 85, Folder 20)
    - Publisher's Weekly, 1977-1979 (Box 85, Folder 21)
    - Pubishing File--Fear of Flying and How to Save Your Own Life, 1972-1988 (Box 85, Folder 22)
    - "Readings, Poetry Conferences," 1972-1989 (Box 85, Folder 23)
    - Redbook Magazine, 1974-1981 (Box 85, Folder 24)
    - Red Cedar Review, 1975 (Box 86, Folder 1)
    - "Requests"
      - "Autobiographing," 1977, 1983-1985 (Box 86, Folder 2)
      - "Interviews," 1975-1987 (Box 86, Folder 3)
      - "Interviews--European," 1975-1987 (Box 86, Folder 4)
      - "Readings," 1978-1980 (Box 86, Folder 5)
      - "Reprint (Essays, etc.)," 1977-1985, (2 Folders) (Box 86, Folder 6 to 7)
      - "Speaking," 1975-1985, (2 Folders) (Box 86, Folder 8 to 9)
      - "Translations," 1974-1985 (Box 86, Folder 10)
      - "TV-Radio-Drama," 1977-1984 (Box 86, Folder 11)
    - "Requiem for a Mouse," 1977-1978 (Box 86, Folder 12)
    - "Reviews," Undated (Box 86, Folder 13)
    - "A Revolution in Consciousness," 1978 (Box 86, Folder 14)
    - "Roald Dahl," 1983 (Box 86, Folder 15)
    - "Room With a View," 1988 (Box 86, Folder 16)